A school teacher gets paid less
than seventy a year, but these
guys treats the homes are
getting 111000. The head that's
one of the top the top guys.
one of the you don't do
anything in the community. In
all reality, they sit on their
**** in the office. Yeah and
doctors and **** teachers are
getting less and they're doing
stuff for us has the city done
any street outreach in the last
year since we've since you've
been here, you guys you guys,
you guys are volunteer and
don't get paid and you guys
have done more than anyone of
them. all of them put together
you guys have done more. All of
them put together.
There's church systems I've
done more than them. There's
people that cook from their own
kitchen and deliver food hot
meals for us that do more than
they do and they're getting
paid that much. That's that's.