My second question is we are
aware that a collision of
lawyers plans on pursuing legal
action against the city related
to the clearing of encampments
in parks. By April 6. Advocates
are concerned that this notice
will lead to mass displacement
of vulnerable people during the
pandemic. Are you still going
to clear the encampments in
early April and why now? I
would just say that what we
have done in this case is to
put together a very carefully
and thoughtfully put together a
plan to move people who are in
encampments in public parks to
better housing to permanent
housing. These encampments are
not safe. They are not healthy
and they do not belong in
public parks. They're not to be
in public parks, but we're not
just clearing them out. We are
proceeding that by extensive
work that is going on right now
to talk to each and every one
of those individuals and find
them better housing housing
that is. Indoors and that is
going to be much more suited to
humane treatment of those
people.